https://jesuitschoolsnetwork.org/privacy-policy/

Communications
Our privacy policy explains the extent to which we acquire and safeguard information from site visitors and network members.
;
Privacy Policy
Tim Sassen
Director of Leadership Development and Communications
If you have questions related to JSN communications, please contact me.
In compliance with guidelines and laws regarding the acquisition and use of personal information by site visitors and network members whom we contact, the Jesuit Schools Network (JSN) operates within the following privacy policy:
Cookies
The JSN web site operates on a WordPress platform that is monitored by Google Analytics. Cookies are used within our site to monitor the duration of visits and page usage within them. No personal information is obtained from site visitors except for when a user voluntarily submits information within a web form.
SSL Encryption
Our site operates under full SSL encryption, so that browsing within our site cannot be monitored by others and information submitted within our web forms cannot be intercepted or compromised.
Email Addresses
In support of its communications work on behalf of the network, the JSN obtains email addresses in the following three ways:
Voluntary forms on our website, such as event registration forms, contact us forms, and email newsletter subscription forms
A request for updated faculty and staff email lists which is sent to member schools each fall
Public faculty and staff email directories on member school websites
In keeping with our pledged adherence to personal privacy, the JSN does not share email distribution lists or individual emails with members of our network or any third parties.
Personally Identifiable Information
The JSN will never ask for personally identifiable information that may compromise your identity, such as
social security number
driver’s license number
bank account information
If an entity claiming to be the Jesuit Schools Network asks you for this kind of sensitive information, do not provide it and contact us immediately.
Contact Tim Sassen
JSN Conference Staff  -  Director of Leadership Development and Communications
Your Name
Your Email Address
Your Message
